{
    "subject": "resource/G._E._M._Anscombe",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Philosopher",
    "human_readable": "G. E. M. Anscombe is a Philosopher.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.79511559009552,
            "question": "In what period did G.E.M. Anscombe conduct her philosophical research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7729385495185852,
            "question": "How did G.E.M. Anscombe's views on language influence her philosophical work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7570910453796387,
            "question": "What are some key themes explored in G.E.M. Anscombe's philosophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7567771077156067,
            "question": "What was the impact of G.E.M. Anscombe's work on subsequent philosophers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7511526942253113,
            "question": "What is G.E.M. Anscombe known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6615998148918152,
            "question": "Who were some influential thinkers that G.E.M. Anscombe's work engaged with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5477451086044312,
            "question": "Can you name some important works by G.E.M. Anscombe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4368669390678406,
            "question": "What field of study did G.E.M. Anscombe specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3995886743068695,
            "question": "What are some of the criticisms leveled against G.E.M. Anscombe's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.387014240026474,
            "question": "Did G.E.M. Anscombe hold any academic positions?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=G. E. M. Anscombe is a Philosopher.",
            "html": "dbpedia_675_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the criticisms leveled against G.E.M. Anscombe's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_675_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study did G.E.M. Anscombe specialize in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_675_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some important works by G.E.M. Anscombe?",
            "html": "dbpedia_675_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_675_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_675_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_675_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_675_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_675_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_675_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_675_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_675_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_675_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_675_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple \"G. E. M. Anscombe is a philosopher\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all the documents mention G. E. M. Anscombe as an analytic philosopher, and one document even provides a detailed description of her work in various areas of philosophy, such as philosophy of mind, philosophy of action, philosophical logic, philosophy of language, and ethics."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe documents clearly indicate that G.E.M. Anscombe was indeed a philosopher, working on various fields including action theory, ethics, and more."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}